Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - DC Citizens for Better Pub. Ed. Bulletin Board, 1971-1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - DC Citizens - Lawyers' CTEE - Syracuse Study, 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - D.C Coalition for Community Leadership in Ed., 1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - DC Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1972-1980 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - DC Commission on the Status of Women, 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - D.C Growth Policy Conference, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - D.C Municipal Research Bureau, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - D.C Psyhological Ass'n, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - DC Street Academy, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - DC Teachers College, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Data D.C Public Schools, 1972-1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Decentralization - Delegation of Auth, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Docket Material, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Draft Counseling, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Driver Education, 1972-1976 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Dunbar High School, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Earn and Learn, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Eastern High School, 1977-1978 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Eaton School, 1976-1983 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Edmonds -Peabody School, 1972-1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Education Accountablity Shared Responsibilty, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Education Commission of the Gates (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Education Commission of the Gates (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Education Development Center Project "M", 1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Education Finance Reform Project, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Educational Facilities Planning Forum, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Comm. On Educational 1977- Programs (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Comm. On Educational Programs - 1975-76 (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Comm. On Educational Programs - 1975-76 (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Comm. On Educational Programs - 1975-76 (Folder 3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum Com. - Misc. thru '74 (Ed Prog) (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Com. - Misc. thru '74 (Ed Prog) (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Educational Law Revision -ADV Comm. (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Educational Law Revision -ADV Comm. (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Elections (Schools as Polling Places ) and Register, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Elementary - Info. For Parents, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Elementary Principals Ass'n, 1972-1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Elementary School Teachers by Grades - Oct. 21 1971 Statistical Report (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Emery School, Undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Employee's Compensation Act, 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Employee Evaluation, 1972-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Employee Relations CTEE (General), 1975-1977 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Energy Conservation, 1973-1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Enviornment Education Program (Folder 1 of 3), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Enviornment Education Program (Folder 2 of 3), 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Enviornment Education Program (Folder 3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Enrollment - Declining Changing, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Equalization - Comparablity Hearing (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Equalization - Comparablity Hearing (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Code of Ethics, 1976-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation and system (ind. Teacher), 1973-1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Therman Evans, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Executive Intern program, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Executive Secretary's Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Exemplary Project - Career Devel, 1976-1977 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - External Affairs CTEE, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Extra Duty Pay, 1972-1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Facilities Planning Unit, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - James Farmer, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Far North- East South- East Council, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - James S.Y. Featherstone, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Federal City College (Folder 1 of 2), 1970-1975 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Federal City College (Folder 2 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Federal Programs (General) (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Federal Programs (General) (Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Federal Programs (General) II (Folder 1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Federal Programs (General) II (Folder 2 of 3), 1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Federal Programs (General) II (Folder 3 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Federal Programs - Impact MD, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Federal Funds - Impoundment, 1973-1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Fed Programs - Bat Inst. Of Educ., 1973-1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Federal Programs -Title I (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Federal Programs -Title I (Folder 2 of 2), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Joint (Federal and Curriculum) (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Joint (Federal and Curriculum) (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Federal Programs - Title I (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Federal Programs - Title I (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Comparability - Title I, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Title I Pac (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Title Pac (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Title I Legal Cases, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Title I - Elem. and Sec. Ed. Act of PL 89-750- Inst. For Neglected and Delinquent, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Federal Programs Title III, 1972-1975 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - ESEA Title III, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Federal Prog - ESPA Title IV, 1976-1977 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Federal Programs - Title V, 1972-1975 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - FED. Programs Emergency School Aid Act Title VII - P.L 92-318 (Folder 1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - FED. Programs Emergency School Aid Act Title VII - P.L 92-318 (Folder 2 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - FED. Programs Emergency School Aid Act Title VII - P.L 92-318 (Folder 3 of 3), 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Financial Conditions Effect on School System, 1972 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Financial Reports FY 1974/FY 1975/FY 1976/1977, 1974-1977 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Financial Statements FY 1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Financial Status FY 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Financial Status FY 1969 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Finance Dept. - Procedures for Reconciliation Process Financial Operations, 1972-1979 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Financial Management Sys., 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Florida- Allocation of School Resources, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Focus on Exceptional Children (Folder 1 of 2), 1977-1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Focus on Exceptional Children (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1976 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Follow Through, 1969-1972 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Food Services and Nutrition (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1977 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Food Services and Nutrition (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation Letter, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Credentials, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Language Program, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Fort Lincoln Newton, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Fortune Magazine, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Marcus Foster, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Foundation for Change, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Francis Jr. High School, 1974-1976 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Speech and of the Press, 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Franklin BLDG, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Friendship Friendship School, 1973-1976 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Galbraith J. Kenneth, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Gay Activists, 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - General Accounting Office, 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Georgetown Univ. Law Center, 1975-1977 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - German Studies, 1972 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Giddings, Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Gifted and Talented Children, 1974-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Ben W. Gilbert, 1973-1978 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Goals, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Goding School, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Gordon Hearings 4-1-76 (Folder 1 of 3), 1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Gordon Hearings 4-1-76 (Folder 2 of 3), 1976 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Gordon Hearings 4-1-76 (Folder 3 of 3), 1976 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Gordon Junior High School, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Grant School, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Grants/Gifts/Donations Indicommissioners' administrative instructions, 1972-1977 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Graves L., 1974-1975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Eloise Bubbles Greenfield, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Guines, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Onnie Haden, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Hair Codes: W.O. Douglas, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Hamilton Jr. High School, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Claire Hancock, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Center for Law and Education "Ineqaulity in Education" - Articles etc., 1972-1976 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Harvard -Roxbury, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Harvard St. School, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Kenneth W. Haskins, 1973-1974 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Hatch Act, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Head Count, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Health - Sickle Cell Disease Genetics, 1972-1976 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Hew Comm. On Education, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Health Comm- Nutrition/Phys. Fitness/Dental/Small Pox etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Health Comm- Nutrition/Phys/Fitness/Dental/Small Pox etc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Health Evaluation - D.C Schools (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1977 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Health Evaluation - D.C Schools (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Health and Welfare Council, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Benji J. Henley, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - History (Folder 1 of 4), 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - History (Folder 2 of 4), 1960-1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - History (Folder 3 of 4), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - History (Folder 4 of 4), 1979-1980 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Hendley School - Arbitration, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - High School - College Internship Program, 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - High School Equivalency Exam, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - A History of the District of Columbia Unit VII: The Center of a Metropolis Washington since 1954, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - A History of the District of Columbia Unit V Washington Between the Wars The Federal Captial Comes of Age - 1919-1941, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Directory of the Public Schools of the District of Columbia, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Birth of M Street High School A Documented and Illustrated Narrative 1892-1898, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Application by the Board of Education of the District of Columbia to the Joint Committee on Landmarks of the National Capital to Designate, Undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - A History of the District of Columbia Unit I: You in History, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - A History of The District of Columbia Unit II: City of Magnificent Intentions, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - A History of the District of Columbia Unit IV: Washington in the Industrial Nation, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - The Black Majority Washington Since 1954 Steven J. Diner, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Hobson v. Hansen, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 7/76- (Folder 1 of 3), 1971-1977 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 7/76- (Folder 2 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 7/76- (Folder 3 of 3), 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hobson V. Hansen 7/75-7/76, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 1/73-12/73, 1971-1977 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 6/74-6/75 (Folder 1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 6/74-6/75 (Folder 2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 6/74-6/75 (Folder 3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Hobson v. Hansen to 6/72 (Folder 1 of 2), 1972 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Hobson v. Hansen to 6/72 (Folder 2 of 2), 1969-1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Hobson v. Hansen 7/72-12/72, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Julius W. Hobson - General, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Hobson v. Hansen, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Julius W. Hobson Jr, 1975-1977 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Resolution Feb 1972 Hobson v. Hansen Mills - DC Special Educ. Etc. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Marv Hoffman, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - John Holt, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Home Economics Curriculum Guide Dept. Advisory Comm., 1972-1975 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Hospitality House, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Houston School Appeals and Grievances, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Howard Univ. Inst for Study of Educational Service, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Harold II Howe, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Human Resources - Dept. of (General), 1974-1978 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Human Resources Transfer of Funds for Medical Examinations - (Vans etc), 1972-1977 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Human Rights Laws - D.C., 1973-1975 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Humanities - Nat'L Endowment for the, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Hyde School, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Immigration and Naturalization, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Illinois, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Indentification Cards, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Incident Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - independent Schools, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Senator Daniel K. Inovye, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Internships - Executive High School, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Inspire - Project, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Installation of New Board Members, 1969-1980 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Instructional Support Services, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Insurance, 1972-1975 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Interaction, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Stanley Jackson Award, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Ken Jadin, 1976 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Janney School, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Dorothy Johnson, 1971-1974 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - John Johnson, 1970-1975 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Jones Playground, 1975 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Diana Josephson, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Judo - Autonomy Correspondence, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Judd Reports etc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Judd Reports etc (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Junior High School Material, Undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Juvenile Court Cases etc, 1972-1973 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Juvenile Justice Project, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Betty Ann Kane, 1976-1980 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Keene School, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Kemp: Memos, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy - RF Memorial, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Kindergarden/Pre-School/Daycare (Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Kindergarden/Pre-School/Daycare (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1975 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Eugene Kinlow, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - kramer, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Lafayette School, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Lamond- Riggs, 1974 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Languages (Latin/French/Chinese etc), 1971-1973 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Language - Lau Case, 1973-1974 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - La Salle School, 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - League of Women Voters D.C, 1971-1976 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Leased Space (Presidential Bldg. and Elsewhere), 1973-1975 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Bill Leauitt - Budget, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Leaves Rules and Problems, 1972-1976 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Mamie D. Lee School, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Reginald H. Lee (Proposal), 1975 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Tunney Lee, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Legal Counsel (H.O Reid etc.), 1973 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Annex Lennox, 1973-1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Letter Heads, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Lettuce Boycott, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Library, 1972-1977 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Light Ship, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln Jr. High School, 1972-1974 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Liquor Licenses '74, 1974 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Liquor Licenses, 1974-1976 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Local Board Agreements, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Local School Plan, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Local (School x School ) Budgeting, 1969-1977 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Nicholas Long, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Lorton, 1974-1975 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Edith A. Lyons, 1965-1973 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - M Street High School (Perry), 1975-1985 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - MacFarland Junior High School, 1974-1977 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Malcolm X's Birthday, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Martin Ruby, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Charles N. Mason Jr., 1971 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Pictures, Undated (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Peace Speech, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - McGoney, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Floretta McKenzie, 1973-1974 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - McKinley High School, 1974-1976 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Hilda Mason - Speeches, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Hilda Mason (Biography) and Photographs, Undated (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Math (and Testing), 1976 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Mathematics, 1973-1974 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Mayor's Office, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Maury School Accident, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts Office for Children, Undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Notices of Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Meetings with Principals etc., 1973-1975 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Mental Health Centers, 1974-1976 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Alice Merritt, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Metric System, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Metropolitan Area Boards of Educ, 1972-1976 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Metropolitan Educ. Council for Staff Development, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Michigan State Dep't of Educ. Ron Edmonds, 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Military Program, 1972-1979 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Military Road School, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Willour A. Millard, 1973-1975 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Mills v Bd. Of Ed Master's Report, 1975-1976 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Mills v. Board of Ed. Dec 1976, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Mills v. Bd of Educ. May 1975-1976 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Mills v. Bd of Educ. May 1975-1976 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Mills v. Board of Educ. Aug 1974-May 1975 (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Mills v. Board of Educ. Aug 1974-May 1975 (Folder 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Mills v. Board of Educ. Jan. 1974-Aug 1974 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Mills v. Board of Educ. Jan. 1974-Aug 1974 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Mills v Board of Education from 01/1973 - Jan/1974 (Folder 1 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Mills v Board of Education from 01/1973 - Jan/1974 (Folder 2 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Mills v Board of Education from 01/1973 - Jan/1974 (Folder 3 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Mills- Draft 12/73, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. From 8/1/72-10/30/73 (Folder 1 of 4), 1971-1973 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. From 8/1/72-10/30/73 (Folder 2 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. From 8/1/72-10/30/73 (Folder 3 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. From 8/1/72-10/30/73 (Folder 4 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Mills v Board of Edu. Sept 1972 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Mills v Board of Edu. Sept 1972 (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. Thru 7/31/72 (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Mills v. Board of Edu. Thru 7/31/72 (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Gladys Mills, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Minor - Employment, 1934-1975 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Mission of Community Concern, 1972-1974 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Mock Trials, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Model School Division, 1973-1974 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Model Cities Funds, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Mongomery County, 1974-1977 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Morgan Comm. School 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Morgan Community School 1972-'75 (Folder 1 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Morgan Community School 1972-'75 (Folder 2 of 2), 1973-1975 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - History of Morgan Community School, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Morgan - Misc. 1971, 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - News - Morgan, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Publicity: Newsapers etc., 1968-1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Morgan Summary - July 1973 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Moms - Virginia, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Motor Vehicle Use, 1972 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Museum of African Art, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Music (Choral and General)(Folder 1 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Music (Choral and General)(Folder 2 of 2), 1975-1992 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Myricks Martha, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Nalle Elementary School, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Names for Schools and Buildings, 1970-1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Nat Cap Area Educational Forum, 1972-1975 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - National Caucus of Black Elected Officials, 1976 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - National Comm. For Citizens in Edu., 1977 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Nat'l Community School Edu. Ass'n, 1973-1975 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - National Georgraphic Building, 1973-1977 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - National Planning Assoc., 1976 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - National Policy Conference - Education for Blacks, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - National School Boards Ass'n 1977- (Folder 1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - National School Boards Ass'n 1977- (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - National School Boards Ass'n 1975-'76 (Folder 1 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - National School Boards Ass'n 1975-'76 (Folder 2 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - National School Boards Ass'n 1975-'76 (Folder 3 of 3), 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - USBA - Washington Fasterport, 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Nonal L. Neal, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Needs Assessment, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood Planning Council #1 Area 5, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhood Youth Corps CETA (in school), 1973-1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Inc. Education Committees, 1972-1976 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Nelsen Report, 1971-1975 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Misc. (Folder 1 of 2), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings - Misc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1972 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - News Releases 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - News Releases 72-74, 1972-1974 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - New York State, 1974-1975 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Nicholas Ave School, 1972-1975 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Education Complex, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Oakland - Califronia, Undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Hugh O'Brian Foundation, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - One America, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Open Space Schools - Ward IV, 1971-1976 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Opening of Schools, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Out-of-Boundary Placements, 1972-1977 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Organization of School System, Undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Oyster School, 1976-1978 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Pacts Office, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Parenting - Parenthood Material, 1976-1977 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Parent - Partners Project, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Parents Manual, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Parents Union, Undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Parking - Presidential Bldg and Elsewhere, 1972-1974 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Passow Report - Exec. Study GR, 1968-1973 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Paul Jr. High School (Folder 1 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Paul Jr. High School (Folder 2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Proposal - Experimental Community Theater - Paul Jr. High Comm. Service, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Peace Action, 1972-1976 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania Assn for Retarded Chldren Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Per Public Costs, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 3)